[{"answer": "Hi, there", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, shit, I've been trying to liaise with you all day. My name is my friend, that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You think this is nasty?  In case you haven't heard. The that place has no charter to operate domestically. Which puts you in violation of federal law", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Special Order 12333 refers to domestic terrorism. You got something you want to", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Swell", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Nice meeting you, too, Special Agent my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Is there a terrorist cell operating in this city that we are unaware of", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You ever been in that place, my friend? You know what happens in there", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Was the blue paint a warning", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "If they wanted to blow the bus then why haven't they blown the bus", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend, my name is my friend, I'm a Federal Agent. We have reason to believe you are an accessory to the bombing of Bus 87", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You are an associate of my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " -- Call INS, find out his status and start deportation proceedings", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, you can't let me do that. What precisely is your involvement with these people", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He can't know we're talking", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Done", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "-- You want to fuck me? Then work with me", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No? Do we really want to have this conversation again? Do we", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Old news", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "We can't release him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Tell me the difference between that and breakin", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Not good enough", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's... against... the... law", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Just because you talk the talk doesn't make you an expert. And just because you read my file doesn't make you an expert on me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Respond, sure. But how", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And if we can't find out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Because he didn't know anything", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Says me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Maybe I'll ask him", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Over six hundred dead bodies", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I ran the network. my friend was the g", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I can't give you pictures because I don't know what they look like. We did everything at arm's length", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I can't give you pictures because I don't know what they look like. We did everything at arm's length", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I've got my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "He's waiting? What's he waiting for? More bodies? We got lots more buildings in midtown, maybe he's waiting to see how many they can blow up", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "YOU DON'T KNOW SHIT HOW I FEEL", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "-- If you're on the that place Terrorist Watch list you cannot get into this country. But my friend was on the watch list, and he got in", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "They told me to call INS", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Look, I thought my friend'd be an easy recruit. He wasn't. It was crazy but I did what I had to do.  You know as well as I do, running an agent can be very... complicated", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You think I'm trying to run you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "The that place received another fax", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Do we? Have him", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "General, do you know that after yesterday's attack, half the parents in this country kept their children out of school", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm saying, the President is prepared to be... Presidential", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What, exactly, are your interests, my friend? You protect my friend, you protect the agency. You're interested in protecting everything but your country", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No, and I don't want to know. With you or without you we're putting my friend in play. Now", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Money... I must have more money..", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I... got it myself", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "my friend will go to ground", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Hit him hard", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Hit him hard", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I've got to stash my friend someplace safe.  Go with God", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Frank... my friend. Junior", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Check this out, pal. His father's a federal agent for ten years", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What about it, my friend", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Works for the Israelis", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I promised we would take care of them. They were working... for us", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I don't know what you mean", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I like watching better", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Nothing's going wrong", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "This is the endgame, you understand that? If this goes wrong", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "We're the that place, something always goes wrong", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "What's over", "docId": "Siege_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Release him", "qsentId": 64}]